Dong She

Personal Profile

A Master's student at the University of Copenhagen, undertaking Computer Science courses. I have 6 years of IT work experience in China, with 3+ years of experience specializing in web development as a front-end engineer, and also with about 3 years of experience specializing in product design as a product manager. Primarily, looking for a student job or internship role.

Education

University of Copenhagen

Copenhagen, Denmark

MSc in Computer Science

Sept 2022 - Current

Anhui University

Hefei, China

Bachelor of Software Engineering

Sept 2012 - June 2016

Work Experience _

Baidu.com Times Technology (Beijing)

Beijing, China

Senior Product Manager

May 2019 - June 2022

- Responsible for product design of growth product module in the Baidu search engine.
- · Realized the growth in the size of the search business by providing users with a better user experience and exploring the latest search modes;
- Significantly boosted the page view(PV) by 5%
- Technical Skills: Product Design, Data Analysis, Axure, Excel, SQL

Xiaohongshu.com Shanghai, China

Front-end Engineer

July 2016 - May 2019

- · Responsible for the e-business front-end development, daily maintenance of the APP pages of product details, shopping carts and payments, member project front-end development and H5 page creations for promotion.
- Technical Skills: JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Nodejs, Python, Vue, Git.

Alibaba Technology Hangzhou, China

Front-end Engineer Intern

July 2015 - Oct 2015

- · Participated in the work of supporting financial cloud business and used AngularJs, HTML, CSS and Gulp to complete the development of the console and web pages for the financial cloud security products.
- Technical Skills: JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Nodejs, Angularjs, Gulp, Git.

Projects & Activities

current A Human-in-the-loop Test Benchmark in ICU scenarios, Research Assistant

CPH,Denmark

International Conference on Network and Information Systems for Computers, Participant

Wuhan, China

2013-2016 Campus social interaction product "Pocket Xiao 'an"., Front-end Developer

Hefei,China

2014-2015 National College Students' Innovation Project, Leader

Hefei,China

Publication

2015 A New Logistics Distribution Scheme Based on NFC (ICNISC-N202), Author

Hefei,China

Skills_

Programming Python, PHP, JavaScript, HTML/CSS, MongoDB, MySQL.

Miscellaneous LTFX, Axure, Microsoft Office, Git.

Language Chinese (Native); English (Fluent; TOEFL 104);

Honors & Awards

- 2015.12 Utility Model Patent Certificate,
- 2014.12 Third Prize for Academic Excellency, Anhui University,
- 2014.12 First Prize in Science and Technology(group), Anhui University,
- 2014.09 Gold Award in 2014 College Students' Entrepreneurship Competition Mobile Internet Specialty,
- 2014.06 Gold Award in 2014 Anhui College Students' Entrepreneurship Competition,
- 2013.12 The Second Prize of "Hefei Lingda Cup" Logistics Design Competition,
- 2013.11 Guoyuan Scholarship of Anhui University,